skype-emoticons.com 2019-07-10

# Privacy Policy – SKYPE

**IF YOU NEED MORE INFORMATION OR HAVE OTHER QUESTIONS ABOUT THE PRIVACY POLICY ON**  
**[WWW.SKYPE-EMOTICONS.COM](http://skype-emoticons.com/), PLEASE CONTACT THE ADMIN VIA E-MAIL BY FILLING OUT THE FORM ON THE CONTACT PAGE.**  
At , the privacy of visitors to this blog is very important. This privacy policy document describes the type of personal information received and collected by  
**www.skype-emoticons.com** and how the personal information is used.

**LOG FILES**  
Like most other websites,  
**www.skype-emoticons.com** also uses log files. Information in log files includes internet protocol (IP) address, browser type, Internet Service Provider (ISP), trace date / time, reffering or exit pages and clicks made by visitors to analyze trends, manage sites, track user activity on the site , and to gather demographic information.

The IP address and other information are not related to personal information.

**COOKIES AND WEB BEACONS**  
**www.skype-emoticons.com uses cookies**  to store information about visitor preferences, record certain user information on pages visited, customize content-based Web pages based on the type of browser that visitors use or other information that visitors submit through the browser used.

**DoubleClick DART Cookie**  
. ::  **Google** , as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on  
**www.skype-emoticons.com** .

. :: The use of  **DART cookies by Googl** e allows Google to display ads that are appropriate to users based on visits on  
**www.skype-emoticons.com** and other sites on the Internet.

. :: Users can cancel the use of DART cookies by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL:

**http://www.google.com/policies/technologies/ads/**

Some of my advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on the site. My advertising partners include: Google Adsense, Chitika & idblogNetwork.

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to send advertisements and links that appear on  
**www.skype-emoticons.com** directly to your browser. They automatically receive your IP address. Other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript or Web Beacons) can also be used by third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertisements you see.

**www.skype-emoticons.com** does not have access to or control over cookies used by third party advertisers.

You should consult the privacy policies of each third party ad server for more detailed information about their activities and to get instructions on how to cancel certain activities.

**The Privacy Policy  ** **www.skype-emoticons.com**  cannot control these activities.

If you want to disable cookies, you can do this through choices in your browser.

More information about cookie management with certain web browsers can be found on each browser’s website.

**www.skype-emoticons.com** complies and complies with the rules under Google. To read Google’s rules, please visit:

http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/
